Guide to the Records of the Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events RG.7.4
New York University Archives
- Series I: Events, 20925
  - NYU in Albany Day 1990 (2/3), 21137 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - NYU in Albany Day 1990 (3/3), 21136 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Resource Network Lunch, Jan 25, 1990; 21135 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Luncheon in Honor of M. Schwarz, Nov 17, 1989; 21134 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Wagner Graduate School Dinner, Nov 16, 1989; 21133 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies Dedication, Nov 13, 1989; 21132 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts and Sciences, Nov 9, 1989; 21131 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - All U Dinner Dance, Nov 8, 1989; 21130 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Successful Aging Conference, Nov 1, 1989; 21129 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Battle for Columbia, Nov 1, 1989; 21128 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - UAA Dinner, Oct 9, 1989; 21127 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Carter de Menil Awards, Dec 10, 1990; 21126 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058074 1
  - Bobst Awards, Dec 4, 1990; 21125 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - World AIDS Day, Dec 1, 1990; 21124 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Ultra Violet Opening, Jan 1991; 21123 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Greeks and the Sea, Nov 1, 1990; 21122 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimo Dedication, Nov 13, 1990; 21121 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimo Dedication, Nov 13, 1990; 21120 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Finance Forum, Nov 10, 1990; 21119 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture: Rupert Murdoch, Nov 8, 1990; 21118 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Chet Huntley Lecture, Nov 8, 1990; 21117 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Music Therapy Clinic: SEHNAP, Oct 18, 1990; 21116 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058073 3
  - President Salinas of Mexico Convocation A, Oct 1, 1990; 21115 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - President Salinas of Mexico Convocation B, Oct 1, 1990; 21114 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - SEHNAP Centennial, Oct 1990; 21113 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Prime Minister Kaifu of Japan Convocation, Sep 28, 1990; 21112 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Federation: Keogh Award, Sep 18, 1990; 21111 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Patriarch of Constantinople, Jul 17, 1990; 21110 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Bassists' Convention, Jun 27, 1990; 21109 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Stern Groundbreaking, Jun 20, 1990; 21108 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Relations: NYU Picnic (1/2), Sep 14, 1991; 21107 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Relations: NYU Picnic (2/2), Sep 14, 1991; 21106 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Relations Weekend, Jun 1991; 21105 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058072 5
  - Dental School 125th: PH Dinner, May 22, 1991; 21104 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Ireland House, May 20, 1991; 21103 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Charles Haughey, PM of Ireland, May 1991; 21102 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Council Meeting and Dinner, May 8, 1991; 21101 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Council: Awards Comm., May 1991; 21100 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Green Thumb '91, Apr 23, 1991; 21099 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Hub N Apple Concert II, Apr 13, 1991; 21098 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Dean Oppenheim Farewell, Apr 11, 1991; 21097 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Distinguished Alumni, 1990-1991; 21096 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Office of Sponsored Programs, Feb 26, 1991; 21095 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Entertainment: Albany Day, Feb 26, 1991; 21094 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - NYU in Albany Day (1/3), Feb 26, 1991; 21093 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - NYU in Albany Day (2/3), Feb 26, 1991; 21092 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - NYU in Albany Day (3/3), Feb 26, 1991; 21091 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Homecoming: Basketball, Feb 17, 1991; 21090 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058071 7
  - Alumni Relations: Homecoming, Feb 17, 1991; 21089 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Alumni: Florida Gathering, Jan 19, 1991; 21088 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Second Annual NYU Picnic, Oct 3, 1992; 21087 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 1992 Alumni Council Dinner, Jun 1, 1992; 21086 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mayor Sobchak Visit, May 1, 1992; 21085 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Park Tragedy, Apr 23, 1992; 21084 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Village Improvement Day, Apr 21, 1992; 21083 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Windows Project, Spring 1992; 21082 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Andreotti Book Reception, Mar 10, 1992; 21081 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - NYU in Albany (1/2), Feb 25, 1992; 21080 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - NYU in Albany (2/2), Feb 25, 1992; 21079 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - All University Dinner Dance, Oct 22, 1992; 21078 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - 1992 Conference: "De Benedetti" Visit, 1990; 21077 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - 1992 NYU Conference, Apr 1992; 21076 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058070 9
  - Bobst Awards Dinner, Dec 4, 1991; 21075 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Havel Information, Oct 27, 1991; 21074 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Havel Guest List, Oct 27, 1991; 21073 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Havel Convocation, Oct 27, 1991; 21072 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Federation Dinner, Oct 23, 1991; 21071 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Classroom Dedication (1/2), Sep 21, 1991; 21070 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Classroom Dedication (2/2), Sep 21, 1991; 21069 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Borris Yeltsin Address, Jun 21, 1991; 21068 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Ireland House Dedication (1/3), Apr 26, 1993; 21067 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058069 1
  - Ireland House Dedication (2/3), Apr 26, 1993; 21066 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Ireland House Dedication (3/3), Apr 26, 1993; 21065 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Stern M.E.C. Dedication, Apr 23, 1993; 21064 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Park Accident: 1st Anniversary, Apr 23, 1993; 21063 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - International Rectors' Conference, Apr 1993; 21062 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 1992-93 Regional Basketball Game Receptions, Jan 13, 1993; 21061 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Fire Plaque, Mar 25, 1993; 21060 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - NYU in Albany, Feb 23, 1993; 21059 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - NYU in Albany Day, Feb 23, 1993; 21058 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058068 3
  - Prime Minister Reynolds Visit, Sep 15, 1992; 21057 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, Jan 28, 1993; 21056 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square News, Winter 1992; 21055 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade, Nov 26, 1992; 21054 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Federation Finance Forum, Nov 14, 1992; 21053 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Varsity Club Awards Dinner, Oct 28, 1992; 21052 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Italian / American Heritage Month Celeb., Oct 15, 1992; 21051 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Federation Awards Dinner, Oct 15, 1992; 21050 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Stern / Coles Volleyball Night, Oct 14, 1992; 21049 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Hopkins-Pechar Golf and Tennis, Oct 13, 1991; 21048 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey Alumni Clubs Dinner, Oct 8, 1992; 21047 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Social Work / Foundling Event, Apr 25, 1995; 21046 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058067 5
  - NYU in Albany, Feb 23, 1993; 21045 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - SSW and Founding Hospital, Apr 25, 1995; 21044 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Albany Day, Mar 1, 1994; 21043 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Albany Day, Mar 1, 1994; 21042 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Science and Math Ed. Conference, 1994-1995; 21041 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend 1995, Jun 1995; 21040 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Council Meetings, 1994-1995; 21039 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Student Senators Dinner, Feb 2, 1995; 21038 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Chet Huntley Book Party, Dec 10, 1993; 21037 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - 9th Annual Albany Day, Mar 1, 1994; 21036 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - 1994 Gallatin Lecture: Shimon Peres, Sep 29, 1994; 21035 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - SSW Dedication, Sep 19, 1994; 21034 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Cuomo / C.A.T. Reception, Mar 21, 1994; 21033 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - H.E.O.P. - 25th Anniversary, Apr 29, 1994; 21032 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Heights Centennial, Apr 17, 1993; 21031 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Federation Political Forum, May 4, 1993; 21030 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - V.I.P. Day, Apr 27, 1994; 21029 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Federation Finance Forum, Nov 19, 1994; 21028 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Musical Theatre Hall of Fame, Nov 16, 1994; 21027 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - President Eanes Visit, Sep 18, 1983; 21026 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Tolbert's Convocation, 1976; 21025 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - President Karamanlis Visit, Apr 6, 1984; 21024 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Varsity Club Dinner, Oct 20, 1994; 21023 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Fed: Varsity Club Dinner, Oct 20, 1995; 21022 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Federation Awards Dinner, Oct 13, 1994; 21021 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, Oct 11, 1994; 21020 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Silverstein Lounge Dedication, Apr 21, 1994; 21019 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - NYU Picnic, Sep 7, 1994; 21018 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Social Work Dedication, Sep 19, 1994; 21017 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Brown Plus Forty, Apr 13, 1994; 21016 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058066 7
  - Shimkin Classrooms Naming, Apr 5, 1994; 21015 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - CAT/ Cuomo Reception, Mar 24, 1994; 21014 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - NYS Commission on National and Community Service, Mar 21, 1994; 21013 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Heyman Hall, Mar 14, 1994; 21012 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - NYU in Albany Day, Mar 1, 1994; 21011 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 1994 "NYU in Florida", Feb 16, 1992; 21010 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Regional UAA Basketball Receptions, Dec 5, 1993-Feb 20, 1994; 21009 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Federation Finance Forum, Nov 20, 1993; 21008 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Seventh Annual All University Dinner Dance, Nov 4, 1993; 21007 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Varsity Club Awards Dinner, Oct 28, 1993; 21006 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Tax Society and Money Marketeers, 1993-1994; 21005 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Finance and Business Club, 1993-1994; 21004 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Westchester / Fairchild Counties Reception, Oct 6, 1993; 21003 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - 1994 Gallatin Lecture: S. Peres, Sep 29, 1994; 21002 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Shimon Peres Visit, Sep 28, 1993; 21001 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Main Building Lounges and Lecture Hall, Fall 1993; 21000 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Annual NYU Alumni Cruise, Jun 6, 1993; 20999 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Jun 1993; 20998 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Council Dinner, Jun 1, 1993; 20997 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Honorary Degree Convocation, Jun 10, 1996; 20996 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Acceptance lists for Convocation and Reception, 1995; 20995 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Academic Convocation: Kim Young Sam, Oct 23, 1995; 20994 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058065 9
  - Kim Convocation: Marching Letters, Oct 23, 1995; 20993 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Kim Convocation: General Invite, Oct 23, 1995; 20992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Kim Convocation: Information Desk, Oct 23, 1995; 20991 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - President Kim Visit, Oct 23, 1995; 20990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Kim Young Sam Visit: General, Oct 23, 1995; 20989 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin Convocation: Marching Letters, Oct 12, 1995; 20988 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Gallatin Convocation, Oct 12, 1995; 20987 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Federation of New York University, Inc., 1989; 20986 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058064 2
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee, 1983-1984; 20985 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Directors Emeriti Committee, 1983-1984; 20984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Tax on Gifts, 1976; 20983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Service Corporation, 1978-1979; 20982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee, 1977-1978; 20981 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Recommendations, 1977-1978; 20980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Federation of New York University, Inc., 1989; 20979 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Federation Nominating Committee, 1988; 20978 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Nominating Committee of the Alumni Federation, Mar 30, 1988; 20977 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Nominating Committee Meeting, Apr 1, 1986; 20976 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Prof. Alumni Assoc., 1984-1985; 20975 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Director of Emeritus Award Past Recipients, 1976-1991; 20974 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - The Federation Annual Dinner, May 24, 1989; 20973 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Great Teachers, 1983; 20972 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Recommendations, 1986; 20971 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee Meeting, Apr 16, 1987; 20970 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee, Apr 17, 1985; 20969 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee, Apr 12, 1988; 20968 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Meritorious Service Awards, Apr 12, 1988; 20967 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Meritorious Service Award, 1986; 20966 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Meritorious Formula Sub-Committee Combinations, 1967-1978; 20965 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1983-1984; 20964 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Budget, 1984-1985; 20963 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Budget, 1985-1986; 20962 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Budget, 1986-1987; 20961 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Budget, 1983-1984; 20960 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058063 4
  - Finance Committee, 1982-1983; 20959 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Finance Committee, 1981-1982; 20958 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Health, Welfare and Benefit Fund Committee, 1982-1983; 20957 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Health, Welfare & Benefits Committee, 1975-1976; 20956 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Health, Welfare, & Benefit Fund Committee Meeting, Jun 7, 1982; 20955 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Health, Welfare, & Benefit Fund Committee, 1979-1980; 20954 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Health, Welfare, & Benefit Fund Committee, 1976-1979; 20953 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Board Plans and Board Meeting, 1986-1987; 20952 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Health, Welfare, & Benefit Fund, 1983-1984; 20951 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Finance Committee, 1983-1984; 20950 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Counts by School, 1982-1985; 20949 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Federation Student Relations Committee, 1984-1985; 20948 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Travel Committee (Federation Committee), 1985; 20947 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Special Services Committee, 1986; 20946 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Federation: Committee on Relations with the University, 1985; 20945 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Black Book Originals, 1986-1987; 20944 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Health, Welfare, and Benefit Fund Committee, 1984-1985; 20943 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Allocation Committee, 1986-1987; 20942 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Health, Welfare, and Benefit Fund, 1982-1983; 20941 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend: Memorabilia, Jun 1995; 20940 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058062 6
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend: Envelopes, Jun 1995; 20939 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - NYU Magazine, 1988; 20938 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058061 8
  - The Friends of LaGuardia Place, Oct 19, 1994; 20937 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Albert Gallatin Lecture: Shimon Perez (1/2), Sep 29, 1994; 20936 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - University: New York University in New York City, Winter 1992; 20935 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Report on Graduate Education in America Pub., 1984; 20934 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Named Professorships, 1981; 20933 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058060 0
  - NYU / Night, undated; 20932 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - The USA Up Close by Giulo Andreotti, 1992; 20931 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - School of Social Work Dedication, Sep 19, 1994; 20930 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Instructions for attaching NYU emblems, undated; 20929 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - International Dimensions at NYU, undated; 20928 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - NYU calendar, 1994; 20927 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Alma Mater, 1989; 20926 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Mitterand Convocation, 1988; 241629 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Ireland House Dedication, 1993; 241630 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Kim Convocation, 1995; 241631 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Gallatin Convocation, 1995; 241632 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - All-University Orientation Guide, 1999; 241633 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - NYU Celebrates 2000 Promotional Material, 1999; 241634 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - NYU Celebrates 2000 Instructions and Script, 1999; 241635 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - NYU Celebrates 2000 Photos, 1999; 241636 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Welcome Day, 2016 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Inauguration, Hamilton (1 of 2), 2016 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Inauguration, Hamilton (2 of 2), 2016 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Honors/Awards Events, 2014, 2016 (Box 43, Folder 1, 3-4)
  - A Celebration of the Life of Nancy Murphy Cricco, 2015 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Series II: Publications, 20852
  - Milton Petrie Lecture, Feb 26, 1987; 20924 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058059 2
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies, Mar 1987; 20923 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Spring Celebration, Apr 4, 1987; 20922 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Leonard Stern Hall Dedication, May 1987; 20921 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - NYU Alumni Cruise, Sep 18, 1987; 20920 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Special Convocation: David Kriser Central Center, Nov 18, 1987; 20919 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - All Libraries Convocation Samples, Dec 15, 1987; 20918 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Milton Petrie Lecture In Entrepreneurship, Mar 10, 1988; 20917 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Second Annual Spring Celebration, Apr 20, 1988; 20916 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Special Academic Convocation: Francois Mitterand, Sep 20, 1988; 20915 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Special Academic Celebration: Alexander Onassis, Oct 10, 1988; 20914 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058058 4
  - Third Annual All-University Dinner Dance, Nov 8, 1989; 20913 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - All-University Dinner Dance, Oct 20, 1988; 20912 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Alexander Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies, Nov 13, 1989; 20911 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - NYU Calendar Book, 1981; 20910 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Night, Nov 15, 1986; 20909 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - The Time Award: Corazon Aquino, Sep 18, 1986; 20908 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Academic Convocation: Dr. Alfred Gottschalk, Oct 28, 1985; 20907 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Courant 50th Anniversary, Oct 22, 1985; 20906 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058057 6
  - Shimon Peres Convocation, Oct 21, 1985; 20905 (Box 31, Folder 2, Box Shared University Archives 002)
  - Alfonsin Convocation, Mar 21, 1985; 20904 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Winter Celebration, Mar 2, 1985; 20903 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Iakovos Convocation, Nov 25, 1984; 20902 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Third Annual Faculty Convocation, Nov 14, 1984; 20901 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - All-University Dinner Dance, Oct 22, 1987; 20900 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Andreotti Special Convocation, Mar 8, 1990; 20899 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - 33 Third Avenue Brochure, 1990; 20898 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - NYU in Albany Day, Feb 27, 1990; 20897 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058056 8
  - Rita Sussmuth "The Future of Europe", Mar 19, 1990; 20896 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Kaifu Special Convocation, Sep 28, 1990; 20895 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Salinas Special Convocation, Oct 1, 1990; 20894 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Kim Convocation - Programs, Oct 23, 1995; 20893 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Kim Convocation, Oct 23, 1995; 20892 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Prime Minister Albert Reynolds' Luncheon, Sep 15, 1992; 20891 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058055 0
  - Alumni in Florida, Jan 19, 1991; 20890 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Founders Day, Apr 18, 1993; 20889 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Founders Day, Apr 8, 1993; 20888 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Founders Day, Apr 26, 1992; 20887 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Founders Day, Apr 21, 1991; 20886 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Founders Day, Apr 22, 1990; 20885 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Founders Day, Apr 16, 1989; 20884 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Founders Day, Apr 24, 1988; 20883 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Founders Day, Apr 23, 1987; 20882 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058054 3
  - Annual Report, 1977-1984; 20881 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - New York University Development Campaign, Sep 1985-Aug 1988; 20880 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - NYU Magazine, 1990-1991; 20879 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - NYU Magazine, 1989-1990; 20878 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - NYU Magazine, 1986-1987; 20877 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - NYU Magazine, 1986-1987; 20876 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - AmeriCorps: Project Safety Net, Fall 1984; 20875 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Gala Dinner Dance, Nov 3, 1984; 20874 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058053 5
  - Invitations for Convocation for Jehan El-Sadat, Mar 25, 1981; 20873 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Runciman Convocation, Oct 18, 1984; 20872 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Fourth Annual Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, Nov 10, 1983; 20871 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - King of Spain Dinner R.S.V.P., Dec 6, 1983; 20870 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - King of Spain Convocatoin, Nov 2, 1983; 20869 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Bobst 10th Anniversary, Oct 25, 1983; 20868 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Convocation, Oct 11, 1983; 20867 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - 1982 Calendar, 20866 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Student Handbook, 1979-1984; 20865 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058052 7
  - NYU 150th Anniversary, Oct 13, 1981; 20864 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Mayor's Proclamation (Sesquicentennial), Oct 13, 1981; 20863 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Night, Mar 22, 1986; 20862 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Havel Convocation, Oct 27, 1991; 20861 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin Convocation, Oct 12, 1995; 20860 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Classroom Dedication, Sep 20, 1991; 20859 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimo Dedication, Nov 13, 1990; 20858 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058051 9
  - All University Dinner Dance, Oct 22, 1992; 20857 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - All University Dinner Dance, Nov 7, 1990; 20856 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Ireland House Dedication, Apr 26, 1993; 20855 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Annual Picnic Sample Info, Oct 2, 1993; 20854 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Founders Day, Apr 18, 1993; 20853 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Founders Day, 1956; 241637 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Founders Day Program, 1957; 241638 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1958; 241640 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1959; 241641 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1960; 241642 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1961; 241643 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1962; 241644 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1963; 241645 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1964; 241646 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1965; 241647 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1966; 241648 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1967; 241649 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1968; 241650 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1969; 241651 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1970; 241652 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1971; 241653 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1972; 241654 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1973; 241655 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1977; 241657 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1978; 241658 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1979; 241659 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1980; 241660 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1982; 241661 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1983; 241662 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1984; 241663 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1985; 241664 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1986; 241665 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1987; 241666 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1988; 241667 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1989; 241668 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Ireland House Dedication Programs, 1993; 241669 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Gallatin Convocation Program, 1995; 241670 (Box 38, Folder 40)
- Series III: Commencement, 241380
  - Commencement Message to Students in Service, 1918; 241674 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Address, 1918; 241675 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Addresses, 1923-1929; 241676 (Box 39, Folder 3)